[
  {
    "question": "1-What is - easy medium question with more than 85 characters. The correct answer is 2",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 2,
    "difficulty": ["easy", "medium"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "2-What is-medium hard question. The correct answer is 4",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 4,
    "difficulty": ["hard", "medium"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "3-What is-easy hard question. The correct answer is 3",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 3,
    "difficulty": ["easy", "hard"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "4-What is-easy medium question. The correct answer is 1",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 1,
    "difficulty": ["easy", "medium"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "5-What is-easy medium question. The correct answer is 1",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 1,
    "difficulty": ["easy", "medium"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "6-What is-medium hard question. The correct answer is 2",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 2,
    "difficulty": ["medium", "hard"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "7-What is-medium hard question. The correct answer is 3",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 3,
    "difficulty": ["medium", "hard"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "8-What is-easy question. The correct answer is 4",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 4,
    "difficulty": ["easy"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "9-What is- medium question. The correct answer is 1",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 1,
    "difficulty": ["medium"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "10-What is-hard question. The correct answer is 3",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 3,
    "difficulty": ["hard"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "11-What is-medium question. The correct answer is 2",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 2,
    "difficulty": ["medium"]  
  },
  {
    "question": "12-What is-easy medium question. The correct answer is 3",
    "answer1": "option1",
    "answer2": "option2",
    "answer3": "option3",
    "answer4": "option4",
    "correct": 3,
    "difficulty": ["easy", "medium"]  
  }
]